in 2048,scince adn technology evolve at an uncontrollable pace.
2048年 科学技术发展得无边无际
unknown drugs and weapons flood our streets and schools
不知名的毒品跟武器泛滥街道跟学校
the contraband is controlled and distributed
黑货由暴力的 匿名的
by violent,faceless criminal organizations
犯罪组织控制跟分配
and the crime rate rises and astounding 400%
然后犯罪率上升到了惊人的400%
ournumbered and overwhelmed,
因为警力有限 犯罪泛滥
law enforcement implements a new strategy
执法机关实行了一个新策略
every police officer is partnered withan advanced
每一个警员都跟先进的
combat_model androld
战斗型机器人搭档
It's an ambush!
是埋伏
John, damn it. I've been hit! I'm down!
John 该死 我中枪了 我倒下了
Pelham! - On the west side!
- Pelham - 在西侧
Pelham's down. I need you to lead me in! We don't know how many suspects are in there.
Pelham倒下 我需要你掩护我进去 我们不清楚里面有多少嫌犯
- Risking one life to save one life... - Shut up!
- 用一个人的命冒险救另一个 - 闭嘴
Lead me in! Move!
掩护我 快!
Hey, buddy. So this ain't good.
嘿 伙计 情况不妙啊
No, it's not. Could always be worse!
不 不是的 没有最糟 只有更糟
It just got worse. They were ready for us, John.
这是更糟 他们就等着我们呢 John
How did Insyndicate know we were coming? How did they know?
Insyndicate怎么会知道我们要来? 他们怎么知道的?
MX! - How'd they know?
MX! 他们怎么知道的?
We're getting out of here. Give me a diagnostic!
我们离开这儿 给我诊断一下
Blood pressure's dropping, celiac artery's blown apart.
血压下降 腹腔动脉破裂
There's nothing to do, sir. We're getting out of here.
- 没救了 长官 - 我们离开这儿
He will bleed to death - before you get him out of here. - Shut up!
- 他会在你救他出去前就死掉的 - 住口
- Cover us! We're leaving! - I cannot do that.
- 掩护我们 我们走 - 我不能那么做
Others have a better statistical chance of surviving. I need to protect them.
数据显示其他人生还的可能性更高 我得保护他们
Are you staying with your partner? You're damn right I am!
- 你要留下来陪你的的搭档? - 你他妈说得对极了
Come back here!
嘿 回来
Come on.
来
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==- 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==- 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==- 机器之心 第一季第1集
-==http://www.ragbear.com==- 机器之心 第一季第1集
-=破烂熊字幕组=- 时间轴：david bowie
-=破烂熊字幕组=- 翻译：省略号想用几个点就几个点的白奶奶 校对：白奶奶背后的男人 时间轴：david bowie
Tell me what you remember. This time...
- 告诉我你记得什么 - 这一次
I remember the radio call. From Pelham.
我记得无线电呼叫 Pelham的
Your partner.
你的搭档
Yeah. - But not much more than that.
是 可除此之外就没多少了
I still can't remember every detail.
我还是记不住所有细节
I want to go again. You made good progress tonight, John.
- 我想再来一遍 - 你今晚已经有很大进展了 John
You were in a coma for 17 months, yes?
你昏迷了17个月 好吗
Technically, we shouldn't be doing this procedure
理论上 在完全康复一年之前
until you've been fully conscious for one year.
我们是不会安排这种手术的
Yeah. Well, technically...
是啊 理论上
you're an unlicensed doctor from SubAsia
你是个来自SubAsia的无照医生
practicing black market medicine.
开黑市诊所的
Well, yes, you can throw me in prison if you want,
是的 你要是想的话 大可送我去坐牢
but... I accepted you as a patient out of kindness.
但...我接收你这个病人是出于好意
You seemed like a desperate man when I met you.
我认识你的时候 你看上去很绝望
And now? Now... you seem like a desperate man.
- 现在呢? - 现在你就是很绝望
John, I know you said the people who ambushed you disappeared,
John 我知道你说过埋伏的人失踪了
but, despite my best efforts, you may not remember who they are.
但是 就算我尽最大努力 你也可能记不起他们的
Most people come to a Recollectionist...
大多数来找记忆恢复专家的人
they want to remember good things.
是想要记起美好的事
Why can't you let this go? It's been two years.
你为什么就不能放手呢 已经两年了
You know...
你知道
they killed my team...
他们杀了我的队友
my friends.
我的朋友
And without this treatment, I can't remember anything.
没有这个治疗 我就什么都记不起来
I remembered something else this time.
这一次我记起了其他的东西
My ex-girlfriend. Anna.
我的前女友 Anna
We were in my apartment.
我们在我的公寓里
Strange. I'll, uh...
奇怪 我...
refine the triggering of that cluster next time.
下次会着重刺激这个记忆群的
Your nose is bleeding.
你流鼻血了
Detective. You all right?
警探 你没事吧?
Yeah.
没事
Where's your MX? I'm off duty.
- 你的MX呢? - 现在是下班时间
- Where's your human? - Talking to a witness.
- 你的人类呢 - 在跟证人讲话
Individuals came over the wall an hour ago.
一小时前有人翻墙
Drive safely. Yeah, I will.
- 小心驾车 - 是 我会的
Message saved for 738 days.
信息保存738天
Hi, honey.
嗨 亲爱的
So, I know you're probably still asleep, but,
我知道你可能还在睡觉 但是...
John, the sun is setting
John 太阳在下山
and it is the most beautiful thing I've ever seen.
这是我看过最美好的事物了
Look.
你瞧
Your father would've loved this place.
你父亲会喜欢这里的
Oh, I can't wait to get back to you.
我等不及回到你身边了
I know I have to wait a week, but...
我知道我要等上一星期 但是...
what I really wish is that you were here with me.
我真的希望你能在这儿跟我一起
Morning. - Morning.
- 早
- You coming in? - I know I said I was ready.
- 你来吗 - 我知道我说我准备好了
Just give me one more day. No. I already gave you one more day.
- 再多给我一天时间 - 不行 我已经给你一天时间了
And another and another. It's time, John.
一天又一天 是时候了 John
John?
John?
I just got a report of a coordinated armed robbery in South Kelvin.
我刚接到报告 South Kelvin发生团伙抢劫
Looks like it was Insyndicate.
看起来是Insyndicate所为
Insyndicate?
Insyndicate?
Okay. I'll come in.
好 我过去
Synthetic calibration incomplete.
人造体校准不完全
I can't access the system. Are you in?
我不能进入系统 你呢?
I'm in. - I'm not in. I'm out. All my files are locked.
- 我能进去 - 我不能 进不去 所有文件都封了
Sounds like Martinez is messing with you again.
看来Martinez又在耍你了
We're supposed to be in a truce, so, if that's true, I'm gonna kill him.
我们应该休战的 所以如果是真的 我要杀了他
Well, there is one other possibility.
还有一个可能性
Did you forget your password again, Detective Vogel?
你是不是又忘记密码了 Vogel警探?
Not bad for a guy who's been asleep for two years.
睡了两年 这精神状态不错啊
I wouldn't say that. He looks weak, to me.
我可不会这么说 在我看来 他很弱
Richard,
Richard
I know this won't be easy for you: don't be a prick.
我知道这对你来说很难 别这么混蛋
This department's handled affairs just fine without him. What's your problem with Kennex?
- 没有他这个部门的工作一样顺利 - 你干嘛跟Kennex过不去?
Don't ask to hear the story... you'll die of boredom.
别让我讲故事 你会闷死的
And exposure to severe envy. Look, there's nothing to envy in him.
- 然后还会看出来很嫉妒 - 听着 我才不是嫉妒
Kennex oversaw that raid, controlled all the intel and got his team ambushed.
Kennex负责监督那次突袭 掌握所有情报 然后让他的人遇到了埋伏
Everyone, except the one man responsible... Kennex... was killed.
每一个人 除了负责人... Kennex... 都死了
Should've been discharged. Richard.
- 应该解雇他才对 - Richard
He won't last. You just watch.
他待不了多久的 等着瞧
Kennex, John. Registration complete. Thanks.
- Kennex John 注册完毕 - 谢谢
Detective Kennex, I'm 785. I've been assigned to you.
Kennex警探 我是785 委派给你的
I'm aware this is your first day back.
我知道这是你第一天回来
I only want to make your acclimation to active duty as smooth as possible for you.
我只是想尽可能让你顺利适应工作
I'm here to attend to all your n...
我要出席你所有的...
I'm not driving with one of those things.
我不会带着这玩意儿开车的
Human partner was good enough for my father.
人类搭档对我父亲来说毫无问题
It's good enough for me.
对我也一样
Since you were last here, MX partners have become mandatory.
从你上次在这儿到现在 MX搭档已经是必须的了
I'm not gonna fight you on some kind of regulation thing, okay?
我不想跟你吵什么规定 好吗
I'm not doing it. - Like hell you're not.
- 我不会那么做的 - 你不会才怪
Have you read Tilden's profile of you?
你有看过Tilden给你的写的侧写吗
And, by the way, he is a very capable psychiatrist.
对了 他是个很出色的精神病学家
"Kennex should return to service never. "
"Kennex应该永远不要回来工作"
- Never? Wow, that's... that's a long time. - "Kennex is suffering
永远? 哇噢 那么久
"Trauma onset OCD, PTSD and psychological rejection of his synthetic body parts. "
"创伤强迫症病征 PTSD 以及心理上拒绝他的人造器官"
Well, that last part is true.
最后一点没说错
Listen, you're the only person more desperate than I am to find out how Insyndicate learned about the raid.
听我说 你是唯一比我还迫切想要查清楚 Insyndicate如何得知突袭的人
If we work together, we can do it.
如果我们合作 就没问题的
This happened a few hours ago.
这是几小时前发生的
Robbery target was an armored truck, carrying bio research.
抢劫对象是一辆武装卡车 载着生物研究物品
If this is an Insyndicate operation, it might help us learn more about them.
如果是Insyndicate的行动 或许能帮我们更了解他们
What's the connection? Parabolic pulse charge was used to stop the vehicle.
- 有什么干系? - 抛物线脉冲充电用于停下这辆车
I haven't seen that since the ambush.
从埋伏之后我就没见过了
Well, sure looks like Insyndicate.
看起来确实像Insyndicate
Inventory report? - That's not in yet.
- 货品清单报告? - 还没出来
Whatever they wanted, they killed four security guards to get it.
不管他们想要什么 都不惜杀了我们四名保安
One of the thieves was shot. He's being treated at County.
其中一名劫匪中了枪 在郡医院接受治疗
John?
John?
Keep the Insyndicate connection between us, okay?
可能与Insyndicate有关的事 不要告诉第三个人 好吗
You think someone in the department's working with them?
你觉得部门里有人跟他们合作?
You're the only guy I trust here.
这里我只相信你一个
Okay. I'll check it out.
好 我会查清楚的
One more thing. Go easy on your partner.
还有件事 别为难你的搭档
Come.
走了
Truck belongs to a private lab run by Omni, company specializing in DNA research.
卡车属于Omni的一间私人实验室 专门进行DNA研究的公司
According to the manager, they were transporting vials of single-strand synthetic, programmable DNA.
据经理说他们在运输 单链合成人造可编程DNA瓶
Detective? Valerie Stahl.
警探? Valerie Stahl
John Kennex.
John Kennex
Pleasure to meet you. - You, too.
- 很高兴见到你 - 我也是
Okay.
好
So tell me what you got on programmable DNA.
跟我说说可编程DNA是什么
Programmable DNA can be used to trigger the process of tissue creation.
可编程DNA可以用于刺激组织合成
For example, to grow sets of organs in humans, possibly for harvest.
比如 在人类体内培植器官 可能用于采摘
What else was taken?
还有什么被劫走了
Acid, bencarmidium, thianel, Myklon Red.
酸 Bencarmidium Thianel Myklon Red
Myklon Red.
Myklon Red
Myklon Red, Myklon Red...
Myklon Red Myklon Red...
Detective?
警探?
Detective, you okay?
警探 你没事吧?
Yeah, I'm fine. Thanks.
是的 没事 谢谢
This sector is Khmer Black territory. They've been known to traffic in biotech in the past.
这一带是高棉族黑人的地盘 过去他们就是以贩卖生物科技出名
We're rounding up the usual suspects.
我们要逮捕的是普通嫌犯
You don't buy it?
你不相信?
Ruby Mah assumed leadership of the gang six months ago when his brother was killed.
Ruby Mah半年前成为了帮派头领 在他哥哥遇害之后
It was controversial. He's seen as too Western.
引起了争议 觉得他太西部了
He needs to show the people he's traditional.
他要让人看到他是很传统的
Today is the last day of the Cambodian New Year,
今天是柬埔寨新年的最后一天
Loeung Sakk, a day of repentance for wrongdoing.
Loeung Sakk 悔改自己犯下错误的日子
He wouldn't commit violence today. This was another gang.
他今天是不会实施暴力行为的 这是另一帮人做的
I find behavioral tendencies in data and identify criminal patterns.
我在资料里查到的行为取向 确认了犯罪形态
Or didn't intelligence analysts do that before I got here?
这不是我来之前 那个情报分析专家做的么?
Thanks. I, uh... I really appreciate it.
谢谢 我...很感谢
Excuse me. Sure.
- 失陪一下 - 好
Tell command we're 10-19. What happened back there?
- 告诉总部我们回去了 - 那边发生什么了?
What are you talking about?
你说什么呢?
It seemed like a petit mal seizure. I will need to report what I saw.
看起来像是癫痫小发作 我需要上报我所看到的
I'm fine. You're not gonna report anything.
我没事 你什么都不用上报
You were in Koln Avenue District last night.
你昨晚在Koln街区
An MX saw you there. I am concerned, Detective.
一个MX 看到你了 我有些担心 警探
That area is populated by numerous black market medical clinics.
那一带有很多黑市诊所
And some tasty noodle joints.
和一些很不错的面店
Look, I appreciate your concern, but there's nothing to report.
听我说 我很感谢你的关心 但没什么需要上报的
Another curious thing, Detective Kennex?
还有一件好奇的事 Kennex警探?
Last night, there were no comestible trace particles on your breath,
昨晚 你的呼吸里并没有食物示踪粒子
indicating you were not there for noodles. I think we should...
证明你并没有去吃面 我想我们应该...
Hey, Rudy.
嘿 Rudy
As I live and breathe.
真不可思议
Or should I say, as you live and breathe? How are ya?
- 还是我该说 你居然活着 - 你好吗
Constantly turning down party invitations.
经常拒绝派对的邀请
I've become quite popular with the ladies. How can I help?
我可受女士们欢迎了 我能帮你什么
I got a rec order for another synthetic.
我拿到了另一个人造物的指令
He fell?
他摔下去了?
Out of a moving car? Yeah, crazy, huh?
- 从前进中的车子上 - 是 很扯吧
Must be some kind of software issue. Gonna need a new one.
肯定是软件出问题了 需要一台新的
Software?
软件?
Since we don't have any MXs available,
因为现在没有现成的MX
department's only cleared one model for active duty. Funny, actually. This, uh...
局里只允许一种模型工作 其实很有意思 这个...
this unit was scheduled to be transferred to NASA next month.
这个是要下个月送去NASA的
It's sad really. He's scrap metal.
很可怜的 他就是废铜烂铁
The trimidium circuits in his spinal column are worth more than the whole of him.
他脊柱里的Trimidium电路 比他整个都值钱
Wait a minute. That's... that's one of the crazy ones.
等一下...这是...那种疯子
What? No. That's rude. Not crazy, per se.
什么? 不 太没礼貌了 其实不疯的
You know, they had their...
就是 他们有他们的...
What? Problems? Who doesn't have problems?
什么? 问题? 谁没有问题啊
Technically, they're perfectly functional. Look at him.
理论上 他们运作良好 你看他
He's road-worthy.
适合上路
John, Dorian. Dorian, John.
John Dorian Dorian John
There. Should be functional. His DF was bad.
给 应该可以用 他的DF不好
Anything I need to know?
还有什么我需要知道的?
Well, the DRN series...
DRN系列
they were based on a program called Synthetic Soul.
他们是基于一个叫人造灵魂的程序
And while he isn't crazy, as you say, there may be some bugs.
既然他不是疯子 用你的话说 那或许是有些故障
Bugs? What kind of bugs?
故障 什么故障?
Some of them had difficulty dealing with their emotive regulations.
他们中有些难以控制情感
Emotional issues. The idea behind the DRNs was to be as human as possible.
情绪问题 DRN的构想是尽可能地接近人类
And the truth is that it's human to have unexpected emotional responses.
事实上 人类有意想不到的情感反应
And if, uh, being as close to human was the goal, then,
如果 接近人类是目标的话 那么
I guess the DRNs weren't such a failure after all.
我想DRN也不算是失败
People have breaking points, and... so do DRNs.
人都有弱点 DRN也一样
So you're saying he's a basket case. Not words I would use, or agree with.
- 那你是说他是个废物 - 我不会这么说 也不同意
All right, plug it in already.
好 已经插好电了
I got to get back on the street. - Okay.
- 我得回街上去了 - 好
Please have the honor of waking him up yourself.
请亲自唤醒他吧
Touch it against his left ear.
触碰他的左耳
How long was I out?
我睡了多久
Uh, four years and three months.
四年又三个月
Detective John Kennex.
John Kennex警探
I'm Dorian. How are you?
我是Dorian 你好吗
Your record is outstanding.
你的事迹太惊人了
Used to be. Excuse me?
- 过去而已 - 什么
Update your files. Let's go.
更新下文件吧 咱们走
Hey, boss.
嘿 头儿
He's on the move. Let's go!
他行动了 我们走
You heard him. Let's go.
你们听到了 出发
So what do I call you? Detective.
- 我该怎么称呼你 - 警探
Well, Detective, this sure beats repairing thermal insulation tiles
警探 这肯定比在C.N.A.空间站
on the C.N.A. Space Station.
修隔热砖强多了
I was decommissioned four years ago, as you know.
你知道 我是四年前被除役的
Why am I in this car with you?
我为什么跟你坐在车里?
I'm required to ride with a synthetic.
我被要求跟人造人同车
I'm not a huge fan of that term.
我不是很喜欢这个词
St. Christopher.
圣克里斯托弗
This has to be a gift from someone. Am I right?
这肯定是某人送的礼物 对不对
Something like 80% of these are given as gifts.
这些大概有80%都是用来送人的
Synthetics are precise.
人造人是很精确的
There's that term again. You just said, "Something like 80%."
- 又来了 - 你刚说"大概80%"
The actual statistic is 83.42%, but I'm running my colloquialism routine,
具体数据是83.42% 但我是运用日常对话
so I express most data conversationally, man.
所以大多数据我表达得比较口语 伙计
Terrific.
好极了
So, who's "A"?
A是谁
Addison? Annie? Adeline?
Addison? Annie? Adeline?
Alana? Anita?
Alana? Anita?
Amy? Audrey? Aquamarine? Okay, that's enough, all right?
- Amy? Audrey? Aquamarine? - 好了 够了 好吗
synthetic off.
人造人停
Synthetic off? Does that mean you want me to be quiet?
人造人停? 是说你想我安静吗?
Yeah, whatever the mode is for you to be quiet, just do that.
对 不管你那个安静的模式是什么 快启动
Hey, man, I can be quiet.
嘿 伙计 我可以安静的
You can just... ask.
你只要...开口
Synthetic calibration incomplete.
人造体校准不完全
Stand by. I'll be back.
等着 我去去就回
Here you go, ma'am.
给 女士
Yeah, give me a black coffee, no sugar.
我要黑咖 不加糖
You got it, Detective Vogel.
没问题 Vogel警探
Officer Vogel, it's good to see you again. Who are you?
- Vogel警官 很高兴再次见到你 - 你是谁
Haven't seen one of those synthetics for years.
好多年没见过这种人造人了
It's perfect. Two cops from the scrap heap.
好极了 两个从垃圾堆回来的警察
This is gonna be more pathetic than I thought.
真是比我想的还悲剧
Those are the models that replaced me.
就是这种型号取代了我
Intimidating. Go register so we can get moving.
- 有威胁感 - 去注册 咱们就可以走了
DRN registration complete. Hey, bot.
- DRN注册完成 - 嘿 机器
Don't snap on us, now.
别咬我们哈
Sir, Detective Vogel's been abducted. Maldonado wants you on it.
长官 Vogel警探被挟持了 Maldonado想你负责
His MX was destroyed. This is all we could get off it.
他的MX被毁 我们只有这些画面
Based on the masks,
从面具来判断
these are the same guys from the armed robbery.
跟劫匪是同一拨人
Suspect back from County?
疑犯从医院回来了吗
Your gang kills four security guards.
你们的人杀了我们四个保安
Now you've taken a cop. Where is he?
现在又挟持了一个警察 他在哪儿?
Did they take him 'cause we have you?
他们把他带走 是因为你在我们手里吗?
You know what this is? It's your booking file.
知道这是什么吗 你的登记资料
It describes the condition you were in when we got you.
描述了我们抓到你时你的情况
Now...
告诉我
What are you doing with programmable DNA?
你们要可编程DNA做什么
What's the Myklon Red for?
Myklon Red是用来做什么的
Oh, look, suspect has a scratch above his eye. I have no idea how he got that.
看 嫌犯眼睛上有抓伤 我不知道他是怎么弄的
Better add it, and get ready to write down "missing molar".
最好加上 准备写"臼齿不见"
There are other ways, Detective.
还有其他办法的 警探
I'm questioning this man, okay, not you.
我在审问这个人 好吗 不是你
Now...
现在...
Synthetic fail. Calibration required.
人造体失灵 需要校准
Synthetic fa...
人造体...
You shot yourself.
你开枪打了自己
Perhaps it was a bit crazy this morning, maybe the doctors at County even missed it,
可能今早有点忙 连医生都没注意
but the trajectory of the bullet that hit you, the burn marks on your flesh...
但那颗打进你身体的子弹弹道 你身上的烧伤痕迹
basically there's no chance that you were hit by a bullet from any gun but your own.
基本上是不可能是被你自己的枪打中的
Is that true?
是真的吗?
You don't know the people I work for. Trust me, I do.
- 你不清楚雇我干活的人 - 相信我 我清楚
I needed to get away from them any way I could,
我要尽可能地远离他们
because there's no getting away from them.
因为你根本无法摆脱他们
Look, we can help you, we can keep you safe, but you need to give us information.
听着 我们可以帮你 可以保证你的安全 但你要给我们情报
No, I'm not safe anywhere, not even here.
不 我在哪儿都不安全 甚至是这里
We'll put you in a secure location under guard.
我们会安排你在守卫森严的安全地点
No one will find you, but you need to talk.
没人会找到你 但你得开口说
I need to be somewhere safe. Then, where's Detective Vogel?
- 我想要去一个安全的地方 - 那么 Vogel警探在哪儿?
What's the address?
地址是什么?
325 Grand, Apartment 6.
325大街 6号公寓
Not that you need me to tell you this, but you just violated the crap out of that guy's civil rights.
虽然不用我告诉你 但你严重侵犯了那个人的公民权益
Fantastic, I get the synthetic with the bleeding heart.
好极了 我这个人造人有同情心啊
Look, I don't care what you're programmed to do.
听着 我不在乎你的程序是怎样
You report what happened in there and you'll find yourself bouncing down the 604.
你要是上报刚才的事 就等着在604大道上乱蹿吧
Detective, if I'm going to report anything, it is because I decided it needed to be reported.
警探  我要是打算上报的话 也是因为我觉得有这个必要
I feel sick.
我不舒服
I need a toilet.
我要上厕所
You all right?
你没事吧
I'll be fine.
没事
Stop. Potential explosive device.
停 有可能是爆炸装置
Humans back.
人类退后
Evacuate the building.
清空大楼
DRN, halt advancement, halt advancement.
DRN 停止前进 停止前进
Detective.
警探
What is it? It's not a bomb.
- 怎么了? - 不是炸弹
That trip wire leads somewhere.
这根绊线是连到某个地方的
I'll lead you in? I do not advise that, sir.
- 我掩护你进去? - 我不建议你这么做 长官
Let's go.
我们走
Vogel.
Vogel
Help! Stay calm.
- 救命 - 保持冷静
Kennex, help me! Help!
Kennex 救我 救命啊
Do something!
想想办法
Bulletproof glass. It's welded shut.
防弹玻璃 都焊死了
Patel speaking. Patel, where are you?
- Patel呼叫 - Patel 你在哪儿?
En route to the safe house. We have the perp in the car.
在去安全屋的路上 嫌犯在我们车上
Okay, turn around... this whole thing's a setup.
好 马上掉头 这是个陷阱
Patel, Patel.
Patel Patel
No, no, no, no...
不 不 不不
Sergeant Patel and two other officers were killed,
Patel警长和另外两名警员遇害
three MXs were destroyed, and the suspect escaped.
三部MX被毁 嫌犯逃跑
It's about time.
正好
I'm sorry.
抱歉
Morgue lab is too slow.
停尸房实验室太慢了
Get a lab box, take a sample of his blood, and send it to Rudy for analysis.
拿个实验盒子 装他的血样 送去让Rudy化验分析
Don't need a lab box.
没必要
I just downloaded the information. Rudy should have the data now.
我刚下载了资料 Rudy现在应该拿到数据了
Why him? Why target Vogel?
为什么是他 为什么是Vogel?
Scan every case Vogel was on.
审查所有Vogel参与的案子
Any connection to biotech, science, medicine, DNA.
任何与生物技术 科学 医药 DNA有关的
I want to see it.
我都要看
I don't know if this is anything, but one of his files is missing.
我不知道这算不算 但他有一份案卷不见了
Case file number 6663. It's gone from all internal records.
案件编号6663 所有内部记录上都没有了
Wait a minute, Detective Vogel told me this morning that he couldn't get access to his terminal.
等一下 Vogel警探今早跟我说 他无法进入终端机
Maybe whoever took him was deleting the file.
或许是挟持他的人删除的
They got into the whole system. Who is they?
- 他们进入了整个系统 - 他们是谁呢
See if anyone downstairs can get that file back. On my way.
- 看楼下是否有人能把那份案卷找回来 - 马上去
The way you said that...
你那么说
you're thinking someone specific is behind this. Who?
幕后主使你有具体的怀疑对象? 是谁
When I want your help, I'll ask for it.
需要你帮忙时 我会开口的
You know what your problem is?
知道你的问题在哪儿吗
Always my favorite part of the day: a synthetic telling me what my problem is.
我一向都最喜欢这个环节了 人造人来教育我
There's that word again. Your problem is, you don't know yourself.
又来了 你的问题是 你不了解自己
You don't trust anyone. Is that my problem?
- 不相信任何人 - 这就是我的问题?
And, man, I don't blame you.
伙计 我不怪你的
After all you've been through, if I were like you, I wouldn't know myself either.
你经历了那种事 要是我的话 我也会不认识自己的
Okay, firstly stop saying "Man. " Secondly you're not like me.
好 首先 别再叫我"伙计" 其次 你跟我不一样
And I'm not like them. MX units are logic-based and rule-oriented.
我跟他们也不一样 MX机器人都是有逻辑 依照规则的
They have no true free will and they are designed to feel nothing.
他们没有真正的自由意志 在设计上就是没有任何感觉的
Now, I can't say that I was born, I can't say I grew in a womb or had a childhood,
我不能说我是人生的 不能说我在子宫里长大 或是有童年生活
but I was made to feel and I do as much as you.
但我是有感觉的 就跟你一样
I read what you wrote: that if an MX hadn't left you behind to save some others,
我看过你写的东西 如果MX没有让你留下来救别人
your partner might have made it out of that ambush alive,
你的搭档或许就能活着离开
and that part may be true, but I read the whole report.
这也许是真的 但我看了全部报告
By the time the ambush had begun, it was already too late and it was you who led them in,
在埋伏开始时  就已经来不及了 是你带他们进去
so you can blame an MX or you can blame yourself.
所以你要么怪MX 要么就怪自己
- Okay, you know what? - I am nothing like an MX-43.
- 好吧 你知道吗 - 我跟MX-43完全不同
You're obviously malfunctioning right now.
你现在明显出现故障了
Why don't you just take a second to reboot yourself? Do not talk to me that way.
- 不如你去重启一下? - 别这样跟我说话
If anyone is malfunctioning, it is you, Kennex. You know what I'm gonna stop doing?
如果有人出故障 那也是你 Kennex 你知道我会停止做什么吗?
I'm gonna stop arguing with a piece of silicon and carbon fiber.
我会停止跟一个用硅和碳纤维做的东西继续吵
Kennex. It's Rudy.
Kennex 是我Rudy
All police in the department are required to have mandatory inoculations
局里所有人都被强制要求接种
designed in police labs for officers only.
是在警局实验室专门为警员研制的
Those inoculations are meant to keep cops safe.
接种是为了保证警察的安全
Protects against biowarfare, gases, pathogens, et cetera.
针对生物战 毒气  病菌 等等其他的保护
We found Myklon Red in Vogel's blood, combined with programmable DNA.
我们在Vogel的血液里发现了Myklon Red 混合着可编程DNA
It targets the inoculation directly.
直接针对接种
It's like getting a hundred different diseases at once.
就像是同时患上一百种病
The immune system goes berserk. What are you saying, Rudy?
- 免疫系统大崩溃 - 你在说什么 Rudy?
That's why his body reacted in the way that it did. That's why he died.
所以他的身体才会做出那种翻译 所以他才会死
I believe Detective Vogel was a test subject.
我想Vogel警探只是一个试验对象
Whoever we're up against... They're targeting cops.
不管我们的对手是谁 他们的目标都是警察
Where are you going?
你去哪儿
I cannot allow you to do this. It's far too soon.
我不能让你这么做 太快了
Look, this isn't about me, okay?
听着 这不是因为我 好吗
Someone is killing police officers, and the only way we're gonna find them
有人要杀警察 我们找到他们的唯一办法
is if I remember more about the people who are doing it.
就是我记起更多关于那些人的事
John, it's not safe for you.
John 这样对你有危险
You do this and you do it now.
你照我说的做 就现在
They were ready for us, John. How did Insyndicate know we were coming?
他们就等着我们呢 John Insyndicate怎么会知道我们要来?
How did they know? How'd they...?
他们怎么知道的 怎么会...
Hey, come back here! You're damn rob...!
嘿 回来 你个该死的机器
I am so sorry. I told him it was too dangerous.
我很抱歉 我跟他说过很危险的
You used my locator chip. Maldonado wanted me to keep an eye on you.
- 你用了我的定位芯片 - Maldonado要我盯着你
Okay.
好
You're lucky you got the partner with the bleeding heart.
你很幸运 有个有同情心的搭档
What did you see... when you were under?
你在里面的时候...看到了什么
I saw someone who was close to me.
我看到有人接近我
Someone who, I realize now,
那个人 我现在意识到
that I should never have trusted.
我根本就不该相信
I want to say I... I'm not even sure it's real, but...
我想说 我都不确定这是真实的 但是...
But it was.
但是的
Who was it, John?
那人是谁 John?
It was my ex-girlfriend.
是我前女友
When I came out of my coma, she had disappeared.
我从昏迷中醒来时 她已经失踪了
Now I know why.
我现在知道原因了
Synthetic fail. Calibration required.
人造体失灵 需要校准
Synthetic fail. Calibration required. I've got a fix for that.
- 人造体失灵 需要校准 - 我有办法
What? It gets creaky sometimes?
- 什么? - 有时会咯吱咯吱乱响 是吗
I've got a fix for that. Olive oil.
我有办法 橄榄油
Olive oil?
橄榄油?
Yeah, man. You put it right on the joint. Olive oil?
- 对 你就倒在关节上 - 橄榄油?
You'll thank me.
你会感谢我的
I suppose I, uh...
我想我....
I should acknowledge the fact that you saved my life.
我应该承认 是你救了我的命
No need.
没必要
I only did it because you're my one ticket. Without you, I'm off the force.
我那么做是因为你是我的单程票 没有你 我就离开警队了
You're lucky I want to be a cop so bad.
我这么想当警察 是你走运
You're not like them, the MXs.
你跟他们不同 那些MX
I don't know why, but you're not. I should take that as a compliment.
- 我不知道为什么 但你就是不同 - 我就当你是夸我了
You should.
应该的
The MX series is based on first order predicate calculus.
MX系列是以一阶谓词演算为基础的
MXs have no intuition, or as you might say, no soul.
MX没有直觉 或者照你说的 没有灵魂
For them, experience, memory is just recorded data.
对他们来说 经历 记忆都是记录的数据
My series is designed to draw conclusions, make inferences.
我的系列是要做出结论 进行推理
The answer is Vogel, right?
搭档是Vogel 对吗?
Who was targeting him, what was the payback for? Yeah.
- 是谁以他为目标 报复是为了什么? - 对
And the only witness we have is Vogel's MX,
我们现在唯一的证人就是Vogel的MX
Who was blown apart when they took Vogel. Yeah, Ru-Rudy said his neural net was completely fried.
- 在他们带走Vogel时被炸飞了 - 是 Ru...Rudy说神经网被完全烧毁了
Worthless to another MX, who wouldn't be able to-to put it together, to make sense of it,
对其他MX也没用了 没办法集中起来 了解内容
but you could make those connections.
但你或许可以联系起来
If we transferred the memory, or whatever's left of the memory from Vogel's MX to you,
如果我们传输记忆 或是Vogel的MX所剩的记忆 传输到你这里
you could make the connection.
你就可以联系起来了
It's worth a shot, Detective. Check, please!
- 值得一试 警探 - 买单
I'm in its short-term memory now.
我现在进入了它的短期记忆
Stand by. I'll be back. coffee... sugar.
等着 我去去就回 咖啡...不加糖
Officer Vogel. It's good to see you again.
Vogel警官 很高兴再次见到你
who are you
你是谁
A few years ago, you logged something into evidence that doesn't belong to you.
几年前 你登记了不属于你的证据
You may remember it as case number 6663.
你或许记得编号6663案件
No?
不记得?
Well, your precinct has been kind enough to hold it in evidence,
你的分局很好心把它留作证据
but tonight, we're gonna get it back,
但今晚 我们要拿回来
and you're gonna help us do it.
你要帮我们这个忙
We've got something they want.
我们有他们想要的东西
Captain, we need to go into lockdown.
队长 我们得封锁大楼
What's going on? They're hitting us tonight.
- 出什么事了 - 他们今晚会袭击我们
They're after something in the evidence room!
他们想要证据室里的东西
Light it up, take out the MXs.
启动 干掉MX
The Insyndicates are on the roof! Come on, now. Go, go, go, go, go!
Insyndicates在房顶上 快点 动作快 快啊
Evacuate building.
疏散人群
Evacuate building. Why are they shutting down and not you?
- 疏散人群 - 他们为什么都死机了 但你没有
They run on a different frequency than mine.
他们跟我的频率不同
Sometimes newer technology isn't better.
有时新科技不见得就好
Come on.
快来
Open the valves.
打开阀门
We got to go through every piece by hand. We don't even know what we're looking for.
我们要亲自动手过每一样东西 都不知道自己要找什么
We know it's here.
我们知道是在这儿
And we know it's valuable because they were willing to kill a lot of cops to get it.
也知道很有价值 因为他们为了得到它 不惜对警察进行大屠杀
There must be some way to restore those evidence files that were wiped.
肯定有办法重建那些被抹掉的证据文件的
I've been trying, but the sabotage was extremely thorough.
我一直想努力 但破坏得很彻底
I'll keep trying.
我继续想办法
Thanks, man.
多谢 伙计
Rise...
起身
and be counted.
派点用场
Stay out of trouble.
远离麻烦
Your father would have loved this place.
你爸爸肯定会喜欢这里的
Oh, I can't wait to get back to you.
我等不及回到你身边了
I know I have to wait a week,
我知道我要等上一星期
but what I really wish is that you were here with me.
我真的希望你能在这儿跟我一起
We're gonna find her, John.
我们会找到她的 John
If you hadn't come back...
要是你没有回来的话...
You saved a lot of lives.
你救了很多人的命
Thanks.
谢谢
Thanks for insisting.
谢谢你的坚持
You put in the rec order.
你下的命令
For Dorian. I checked out his record.
Dorian 我查了他的记录
It's mostly redacted, but I saw that it was you who put in the request for me to get him. Why?
大部分都改动过 但我看到是你让我去找他的 为什么
The DRN is good for you.
DRN对你有帮助
Sandra... you didn't answer my question.
Sandra...你没有回答我的问题
Why Dorian? 'Cause he's special.
- 为什么是Dorian? - 因为他很特别
Just like you. See you at roll call.
就像你 点名时见
I assume you want quiet mode, Detective?
我想你需要安静模式 是吧 警探
Not necessarily.
没必要
Call me John.
叫我John
破烂熊字幕组 -==http://www.ragbear.com==- 欢迎加入
破烂熊字幕组 -==http://www.ragbear.com==- 欢迎加入